Guide to the Office of the Provost records, 1944-2011 RG0037
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Office of the Provost records
1944-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Office of the Provost
RG0037
50 Linear Feet
Collection includes correspondence, by-laws, affirmative action plans, memos, meeting minutes, agendas, and reports.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1 and 3 are closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation. Series 8 is closed for 75 years from date of creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Office of the Provost.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Office of the Provost at The George Washington University was created in 1969 as the Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs. The position was the chief administrative officer under the President, working with, admissions, academics, and affirmative action programs on campus. Oswald C. Colclough, who was twice acting President of GW, served as Provost from 1961-64. Harold F. Bright served in the post from 1969-74, and was succeeded by William D. Johnson, who served from 1984-89, when the position was abolished to streamline administration.
In 2003 the position was reinstituted, with the charge to oversee the offices of communication and governmental, international, and corporate affairs, as well as handling daily administrative duties during the President's absence. Dr. John L. "Skip" Williams, Dean of the School of Medicine and Health Sciences was the first person to hold the newly revitalized post. The Provost reports to the President.
The Office of Associate Provost was created in 1984, with Marianne R. Phelps as head. This position was responsible for the coordination of all equal employment and affirmative action programs at the university. In 1985 the office published the report of the Commission for the Year 2000, which examined the academic future of the University.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include correspondence, by-laws, affirmative action plans, memos, meeting minutes, agendas, and reports. They range in date from 1973-2011, and were transferred to the University Archives by the University Provost. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into eight series: Office files; Commission on Equal Opportunity; Office files; Division of Extension; Commission for the Year 2000; Department planning reports; Office files; and Accession 2014.023.
Washington (D.C.); Affirmative action programs; By-laws; George Washington University; Colclough, Oswald S.
- Office files, 1965-1988; RG0037 Series 1; 40 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of office files relating to Ben Franklin University, Omicron Delta Kappa, Provost Office budget, admissions, registrar, university historian, School of Education, College of General Studies, National Law Center, School of Engineering, University Library, athletics, student activities, residence halls, Marvin Center, University Club, and chronological files. The materials range in date from 1965-88.
  - Advisory Committee: Year 2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Office: American Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    General note
    Miscellaneous
  - Benjamin Franklin University Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Benjamin Franklin University Correspondence, 10/1987-11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Benjamin Franklin University Correspondence, 08/1987 --09/1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Benjamin Franklin University Correspondence, 08/1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    File may contain material prior to listed date
  - Benjamin Franklin University Returned Mail, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Budget Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Continuing Education Tidewater Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Center for Social Policy Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Colonials Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbian College, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Columbian College, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Computer Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    CAAC; original finding aid does not explain abbreviation
  - Computer Usage Fees, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Communications: Television Station, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Communications: Radio, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Conflict of Interest Statements: A-M, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Conflict of Interest Statements: N-Z, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Comptroller, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller Search, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Development Office, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Division for Continuing Education: National Center for Innovation in Corrections, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EEO, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Original finding aid does not explain abbreviation
  - Electronet, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Endowed Fellowships, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Committee on Appointments, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Gelman Library: Grad Ads and Invitations, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Law School: General, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Medical Center, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Middle States: Visit, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Navy Reserve Officer Training Corps, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Personnel: Personel Benefits, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Personnel: Service Awards, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Personnel: Prof Sharkey Retirement, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - President Elliott's Retirement, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - President Elliott's Portrait, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Prison Industries' Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Registration, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Retirement: Tax Reform, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - School of Engineering and Applies Sciences, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    General
  - School of Engineering and Applies Sciences P/R Investigation, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - School of Engineering and Applies Sciences Budget Materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Department, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Security, 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Smith Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Space Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Student Accounts/Payment Problems, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - TIAA-Cref Study Committee, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Virginia State Corporation Commission, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Visitors and Guests, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wellness Program, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Year End, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Provost Office Budge, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - University Relations, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee: Year 2000, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Issues, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Consortium: Latin American Studies, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Compensation Policy Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Senate Committee: Planning and Budgeting, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Consortium TV Cable Task Force, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Consortium East Asian Art, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Center for Naval Analysis, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Early Retirement Systems, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Council on Doctoral Programs, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Senate Committee on Faculty Salaries, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Retention Committee, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Federal Fair Labor Standards Act, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Group Budget Summary Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Provost Chronological File, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Provost Chronological File [1/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Provost Chronological File [2/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Provost Chronological File [3/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Provost Chronological File [4/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Provost Chronological File [5/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Provost Chronological File [6/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Provost Chronological File [7/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Provost Chronological File [8/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Provost Chronological File [9/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Provost Chronological File [10/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Provost Chronological File [11/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Provost Chronological File [12/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Provost Chronological File [13/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Provost Chronological File [14/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Provost Chronological File [15/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Provost Chronological File [16/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Provost Chronological File [17/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Provost Chronological File [18/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Provost Chronological File [19/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Provost Chronological File [20/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Provost Chronological File [21/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Provost Chronological File [22/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Provost Chronological File [23/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Provost Chronological File [24/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Provost Chronological File [25/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Provost Chronological File [26/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Provost Chronological File [27/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Provost Chronological File [28/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Provost Chronological File [29/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Provost Chronological File [30/30], 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Student Accounts, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Student Accounts, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Student Accounts, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Space Committee, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Senate Committee Planning and Budgeting, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Compensation Policy Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Senate Committee: Appointed Salary and Fringe Benefits, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Council of Deans, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Council of Deans, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Council of Deans, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Accreditation, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Salaries: Policy File, 1966-1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Salaries: AAUP Bulletin, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Salaries: Salary Scale--AAUP, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Salaries: Salary Studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Salaries: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Salaries: Projections, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SEAS: Accreditation, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - President, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Data Processing, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Computer Center, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs, 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vice President of Administration, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Program Policy Studies, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Business Office, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Business Office, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Business Office, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Business Office, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Personnel, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Research, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Admissions, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Registrar, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Student Affairs, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Vice President of Development, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Editor of Academic Publications, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Staff Benefits, 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - First Summer Session, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Summer Sessions Special Program, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Second and Third Summer Sessions, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Special Programs, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Summer Sessions, 1975-1967 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Staff Benefits Adjustments to twelve percent, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Budget Reconciliation, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Budget Reconciliation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Budget Summary, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Summary Sheets, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Budget Reconciliation, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Non-Academic Salary Inc., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Non-Academic Salary Inc., 07/01/1976 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    File may include materials prior to the listed date
  - Budget Change Requests Made, 07/01/1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Budget Call, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Budget Change Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Transmittal Letters Instructions, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Transmittals, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - 1974-1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - DP, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Transmittals, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Staff Benefits Distribution, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Transmittals, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - University Historian, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Student Health Services, 1969-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Budget Change Request: Control and Records, 1968-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Columbian College, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Columbian College, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - School of Education, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - School of Education, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - School of Education, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - School of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - College of General Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - College of General Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - College of General Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Continuing Education for Women, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - College of General Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Government and Business Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Budgets Pending, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Proposals
  - Summaries: Board, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller Working Budget, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Registrars Statistics: Student Services, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - AAMC Program for Cost Finding Procedures for Medical Colleges, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Registrar's Statistics, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Dean, Division of University Students, 1969-1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Government & Business Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - International Program Development, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Government and Business, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Forensic Science, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Graduate School, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Law Center, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - National Law Center, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - National Law Center, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - National Law Center, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Summer Sessions, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Summer Sessions, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Summer Sessions, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Summer Sessions, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - School of Public and International Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - School of Public and International Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - School of Public and International Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - School of Public and International Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - University Library, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - University Library, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - University Library, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - University Library, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - New Library Expenses, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - University Library, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Library Budget, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Physical Plant, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Physical Plant, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Physical Plant Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Athletics, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Athletics, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Director of Athletics, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Athletics, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Athletics: Projection, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Student Activities, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Student Activities, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    Publications
  - Student Activities, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Student Activities, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Student Activities, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Student Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Dramatic Activities, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Residence Halls, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Residence Halls, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Residence Halls, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Residence Halls, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Residence Halls, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Residence Halls: Budget Request Changes, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Marvin Center, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Marvin Center, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Marvin Center, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Marvin Center, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Overhead Rates, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - EOP Summer Session Tuition, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Marvin Center, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Budget Change Request [1/3], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Budget Change Request [2/3], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Budget Change Request [3/3], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Budget Change Request [1/3], 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Budget Change Request [2/3], 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Budget Change Request [3/3], 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Budget Change Request [1/3], 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Budget Change Request [2/3], 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Budget Change Request [3/3], 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 07/1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Chronological File, 05/1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Chronological File, 04/1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chronological File, 03/1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Chronological File, 02/1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Chronological File, 01/1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Chronological File, 12/1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Chronological File, 11/1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Chronological File, 10/1976 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chronological File, 09/1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Chronological File, 08/1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, 07/1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Physical Exam Reimbursement, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, 06/1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, 05/1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, 04/1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, 03/1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File, 01/1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File, 12/1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Physical Exam Reimbursements, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - IP's JV Budget Change Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Fiscal, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Fiscal, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Fiscal, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Duplicating Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Chronological File, 01/1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Chronological File, 02/1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Chronological File, 03/1973 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Chronological File, 04/1973 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Chronological File, 05/1973 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Chronological File, 06/1973 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Chronological File, 07/1973 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Chronological File, 08/1973 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Chronological File, 09/1973 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Chronological File, 10/1973 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Chronological File, 11/1973 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Chronological File, 12/1973 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Chronological File, 01/1974 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Chronological File, 02/1974 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Chronological File, 03/1974 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Chronological File, 04/1974 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Chronological File, 05/1974 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Chronological File, 06/1974 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Chronological File, 07/1974 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Chronological File, 08/1974 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Chronological File, 09/1974 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Chronological File, 10/1974 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Chronological File, 11/1974 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Chronological File, 12/1974 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Chronological File, 01/1975 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Chronological File, 02/1975 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Chronological File, 03/1975 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Chronological File, 04/1975 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Chronological File, 06/1975 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Chronological File, 07/1975 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Chronological File, 08/1975 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Chronological File, 09/1975 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Chronological File, 10/1975 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Chronological File, 11/1975 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - General Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - General Administration, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    File may contain materials before listed date
  - Cost Sharing, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Consortium, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Chronological File, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Faculty and Personnel Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Chronological File, 07/1972-12/1972 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Chronological File, 06/1972 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Chronological File, 05/1972 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Chronological File, 04/1972 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Chronological File, 03/1972 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Chronological File, 02/1972 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Chronological File, 01/1971 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Chronological File, 02/1971 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Chronological File, 03/1971 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Chronological File, 04/1971 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Budget Assembly Budget Change Requests, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Budget Assembly Reconciliations, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Budget Transmittals, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Budget Transmittals, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - General Budget Policy Guidelines, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Teaching Assistant and GTF Compensation, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Personnel Miscellaneous Information, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Budget Reconciliations, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Wang-Payroll/Personnel System, 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)